brokeprofessionals.com 2014-12-20

# Privacy Statement | Broke Professionals

WWW.BROKEPROFESSIONALS.COM (hereinafter referred to as “We”) has created this [privacy statement](http://www.brokeprofessionals.com/privacy-statement/ "privacy statement") for www.brokeprofessionals.com in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. Accordingly, below discloses the privacy statement and privacy practices of this site.

**Information Automatically Logged**  
This site may log your IP address to help diagnose problems with the web server and to administer this web site and such information will be used for general traffic tracking and security as through the web-host, etc..

**Cookies**  
This site may use cookies to track information [about](http://www.brokeprofessionals.com/about-2/ "about") its visitors to see pages viewed, etc.

**Subscription to Website**  
This site provides order forms for you to subscribe to an RSS feed, etc.  Any such information freely provided by you at this time will be completely private and shall only be used for purposes of keeping track of subscribers.  This website will never sell your information provided or otherwise use it other than in the standard use of the website.  Additonally, to subscribe the website has very little required/requested information.  Do not subscribe or provide any such information if you are not over 18 years of age.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. This site and its owner(s) are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites which are provided as links.

**Public Forums**

This site may make chat rooms, forums,  comments, message boards, and/or other such avenues available to people visiting the site/blog.  Any such information disclosed available to its visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas shall by their very nature become public information.  Accordingly, please exercise caution when you decide to disclose such personal information.  Again, please do not use these features unless you are at least 18 years of age.

**Security**

This Site and its owners will not be held liable for any technical problems, including but not limited to trojans, worms, viruses, etc.  The site does what it can to remain free of such issues.  However, sometimes issues occur which are outside our control.  It is not our intent for anyone to have such issues, but please take the proper precautions while accessing any website and make sure your antivirus, etc., is up to date.

Thank you in advance for your time and consideration.  Should you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to email me at webhost@brokeprofessionals.com
